http://www.acrelectronics.com/t&cprivacy/privacy

Inland Emergency Boating Supplies
Boating and water sports emergency supplies such as PLBs, EPIRBs, strobelights, search lights, and more.
Nearshore Boating Emergency Supplies
ACR is the leader for nearshore boating supplies such as personal locator beacons, EPIRBs, survivor kits, and more.
Off Shore Boating Safety Products
ACR is the #1 manufacturer for all your off shore boating safety products.
Commercial Boating Safety Products
Purchase all your commercial safety boating products such as EPIRBs, PLBs and more from the most trusted brand by thousands of boaters.
View all Marine
Outdoor
Hiking / Climbing / Camping Boating Safety Products
ACR is the #1 website to purchase all your hiking emergency related gear.
Action Sports and Cycling Emergency Safety Products
Stay safe and prepared with ACR's safety products for action sports enthusiasts.
Travel Emergency Products
Stay safe while traveling with ACR's safety products.
Paddle Boat Sports / Fishing Boat Safety Products
Paddle boat safety is important so make sure you consider bringing along the right safety products such as a PLB with you when you head out on the water.
View all Outdoor
Aviation
Aviation Safety Equipment
ACR is the #1 aviation safety equipment manufacturer. ELTs (Emergency Locator Transmitter) can be purchased on our site. Take to the skies with self confidence that you are using the right safety products.
Business Jet
Small Jet, Turboprop
Rotocraft
Turbine Helicopter, Piston Helicopter
Commercial Aircraft Emergency Products
ACR is the leader commercial aircraft emergency equipment.
View all Aviation
Military
Police / Municipality
Federal, state, local
Air Patrol
Pilots, fighter planes
Naval
Task forces, warships
Ground / Special Forces Emergency Equipment
Ground or special forces can stay safe with ACR's emergency equipment. The #1 trusted brand since 1956, know that you are in good hands with a company that is focused on creating high quality products.
View all Military
Support
Register Your Beacon
Warranty
Dealer Locator
Return and Exchanges
Repairs
Technical Support
FAQs
Declaration of Conformity
Contact Us
Company
/ About us
/ Acr electronics, inc.
/ Artex
/ Flight data systems
/ Latitude technologies
/ Nal research
/ Ocean signal
/ Freeflight systems
/ Skytrac
/ United moulders
/ Quality
/ Capability
/ Careers
Language
English (US)
Español
Français (FR)
Language
English (US)
Español
Français (FR)
Account Settings
Sign in
Create an account
Building survival Products since 1956
\\
/ Sign In
/ Create An Account
Language
English (US)
Español
Français (FR)
Language:en
English (US)
Español
Français (FR)
0
marine
Shop safety products by activity
Inland Emergency Boating Supplies
Boating and water sports emergency supplies such as PLBs, EPIRBs, strobelights, search lights, and more.
Nearshore Boating Emergency Supplies
ACR is the leader for nearshore boating supplies such as personal locator beacons, EPIRBs, survivor kits, and more.
Off Shore Boating Safety Products
ACR is the #1 manufacturer for all your off shore boating safety products.
Commercial Boating Safety Products
Purchase all your commercial safety boating products such as EPIRBs, PLBs and more from the most trusted brand by thousands of boaters.
View all Products de Marine
outdoor
Shop safety products by activity
Hiking / Climbing / Camping Boating Safety Products
ACR is the #1 website to purchase all your hiking emergency related gear.
Action Sports and Cycling Emergency Safety Products
Stay safe and prepared with ACR's safety products for action sports enthusiasts.
Travel Emergency Products
Stay safe while traveling with ACR's safety products.
Paddle Boat Sports / Fishing Boat Safety Products
Paddle boat safety is important so make sure you consider bringing along the right safety products such as a PLB with you when you head out on the water.
View all Products de Outdoor
aviation
Shop safety products by activity
Aviation Safety Equipment
ACR is the #1 aviation safety equipment manufacturer. ELTs (Emergency Locator Transmitter) can be purchased on our site. Take to the skies with self confidence that you are using the right safety products.
Business Jet
Small Jet, Turboprop
Rotocraft
Turbine Helicopter, Piston Helicopter
Commercial Aircraft Emergency Products
ACR is the leader commercial aircraft emergency equipment.
View all Products de Aviation
military
Shop safety products by activity
Police / Municipality
Federal, state, local
Air Patrol
Pilots, fighter planes
Naval
Task forces, warships
Ground / Special Forces Emergency Equipment
Ground or special forces can stay safe with ACR's emergency equipment. The #1 trusted brand since 1956, know that you are in good hands with a company that is focused on creating high quality products.
View all Products de Military
Survivor Club
News
Support
/ Register Your Beacon
/ Warranty
/ Dealer Locator
/ Return and Exchanges
/ About us
/ Acr electronics, inc.
/ Artex
/ Flight data systems
/ Latitude technologies
/ Nal research
/ Ocean signal
/ Freeflight systems
/ Skytrac
/ United moulders
/ Quality
/ Capability
/ Careers
Register Your Beacon
T&Cs and Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions - Legal Notice
ACR / Artex (ACR Electronics, Inc.) has taken all reasonable care to ensure that the information on this website was accurate at the time of its initial inclusion. However, no warranty, condition or representation, express or implied, is made or given that the information is free from errors, inaccuracies or omissions. Furthermore, the information may be subject to change or update without notice and must not be taken as establishing any contractual or other commitment binding upon ACR Electronics, Inc. or any of its subsidiary or associated companies.
This site may provide links to third-party sites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the ACR / Artex Site. ACR Electronics, Inc. nor its subsidiaries or associated companies control those sites and do not endorse directly or indirectly any information or make any representations about third-party sites or the owners and ACR Electronics, Inc. are not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement made through the site by any party other than ACR Electronics, Inc. or any content provided on linked sites or the capabilities or reliability of any product or service obtained from a linked site.
No information contained in this site constitutes an invitation to deal or otherwise invest in ACR Electronics, Inc.'s shares. In the event of any discrepancy between any version of the annual or half-yearly results appearing on this website and the hard copy as posted to shareholders, the hard copy must be taken to be the correct version.
Any comments, reviews, stories, media or materials sent to ACR Electronics, Inc. or any of its subsidiaries or associated companies through this site, including suggestions and responses to questions, shall be deemed to be non-confidential. ACR shall have all rights to such comments and materials and may use them as it sees fit.
Terms and Conditions - Copyright
The copyright, trademarks, logos and service marks ("Marks") displayed on the ACR / Artex website are the property of ACR Electronics, Inc. and other parties. Users are prohibited from using any Marks for any purpose other than the purposes of this site without the written permission of ACR Electronics, Inc. or such third party which may own the Marks. All information and content available on or through the ACR Electronics, Inc. website ("Content") is protected by copyright. Users are prohibited from modifying, copying, distributing, transmitting, displaying, publishing, selling, licensing, creating derivative works or using any Content available on or through the ACR Electronics, Inc. site for commercial or public purposes.
Terms and Conditions - Disclaimer
Whilst all reasonable care has been taken in the preparation of this site no liability is accepted under any circumstances by ACR Electronics, Inc. nor its subsidiaries or associated companies for any loss incurred as a result of reliance on any statement, error or any omission contained herein, including without limitation direct, indirect or consequential damages however arising from your use of the ACR website or any website to which this website is linked.
All content on the ACR Electronics, Inc. site is provided to you "as is" without warranty of any kind either express or implied including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, title, non-infringement, security or accuracy.
The statements within this site reflect our understanding of current and proposed legislation, which may change without notice.
The content of this site should not be regarded as specific advice in relation to the matters addressed.
Nothing in these terms and conditions limits our liability for death or personal injury resulting from our negligence.
These terms and conditions and any disputes shall be governed by and in accordance with law and subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the United States of America courts.
Privacy Policy - Privacy Statement - ACR / ARTEX Products
ACR Electronics, Inc. ("ACR") doing business as ACR / Artex is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Privacy Statement applies to the website you are currently viewing ("the Site") and governs data collection and usage. By accessing, browsing and/or using the Site, you consent to the data practices described in this Statement and agree to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.
Privacy Policy - Use of Your Personal Information
ACR Electronics, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate the Site and deliver the services you have requested. ACR Electronics, Inc. also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from ACR Electronics, Inc. and/or its affiliates. ACR Electronics, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Information you disclose may also be disclosed without your consent to companies and individuals employed to perform services on ACR Electronics, Inc. behalf, such as customer service representatives, marketing and credit card processing companies. Finally, personal information ACR Electronics, Inc. has collected may be passed on to a third party without your consent in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of ACR Electronics, Inc.
ACR Electronics, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. ACR Electronics, Inc. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, ACR Electronics, Inc. may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail or arrange for deliveries.
ACR Electronics, Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
ACR Electronics, Inc. will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ACR Electronics, Inc. or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ACR Electronics, Inc. ; and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ACR Electronics, Inc. , or the public.
Privacy Policy - Use of Cookies
The Site uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the ACR Electronics, Inc. features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site.
Privacy Policy - Disclaimer
ACR Electronics, Inc. cannot guarantee that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Statement. As a user of this Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Site. For further information, please consult ACR Electronics, Inc. General Terms and Conditions of Use, which are incorporated herein by reference.
Privacy Policy - Changes to This Statement
ACR Electronics, Inc. may, in its discretion, make changes to this Statement. When ACR Electronics, Inc. makes changes to the Statement, it will give notice to you by posting the revised Statement on the Site. ACR Electronics, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how ACR Electronics, Inc. is protecting your information.
Privacy Policy - Contact Information
ACR Electronics, Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Statement. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Statement, please email us via the contact us form on the Site.
© Copyright 2014 ACR Electronics, Inc.
All rights reserved worldwide.
Privacy Policy - Collection of Your Personal Information
ACR Electronics, Inc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. ACR Electronics, Inc. also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by ACR Electronics, Inc.. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. This information is generally used by ACR Electronics, Inc. for the operation of the services it provides, to maintain the quality of such services, and to compile general statistics regarding use of the Site.
Please keep in mind that if you disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through public message boards available on the Site, this information may be collected and used by others.
ACR Electronics, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to from the Site so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. Cobham Beacon Solutions is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on such web sites.
We use SessionCam on our website to help us understand the behavior of our website visitors. SessionCam will collect information such as the details of mouse movements, page scrolling and click activity of individual visitors. SessionCam may also record data entered into our website forms. We use the data collected by SessionCam to identify where visitors struggle the most so that we can improve these areas of our website.
Dealer Locator
About Us
Dealer Login
Quality
Capabilities
Careers
Follow Us
Returns and Exchanges
We Build Quality Products Knowing They Are Used To Save Lives™
© 2018
ACR Electronics, Inc. 5757 Ravenswood Road, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33312 USA.
